panago.com 2018-09-21

# Privacy Policy | Pizza Home Delivery | Panago Pizza

At Panago Pizza, we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the personal information that you entrust to us. Our Privacy Policy describes the type of information we collect, how we use that information, and the security measures that we put in place to protect it. We also outline how to contact us should you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or if you wish to remove your personal information from our customer database.

* * *

### WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION DOES PANAGO COLLECT?

Each time you place an order with Panago, we collect the personal information that is required to help process and fulfill your pizza order. This personal information includes your name, phone number, address, and the details of the Panago products and services you are ordering.

### HOW IS THIS INFORMATION USED?

Your personal information is stored in our customer database to help us serve you better in the future. We recognize that there are important order and delivery details we need to make note of to ensure we can continually serve you better. Our goal is to make your experience of ordering pizza as easy and enjoyable as possible.  
We also maintain a recent purchase history of the products and services you buy and from time to time we may analyze this information to better understand your needs and preferences. In addition, we may occasionally call you to ask for your feedback in an effort to ensure you are happy with the products and service you are receiving.

### STORAGE, SECURITY AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION:

We retain your personal information in our customer database and we utilize security measures to keep your information safe. We will not share or sell any of your personal information to another company, with the exception of companies that we partner with to manage one of the tasks described within this policy. Any company that we partner with has an obligation to keep the information completely confidential and will not use or disclose your information for any purpose other than those identified in this policy.

### REMOVAL OF PERSONAL INFORMATION:

Personal information is retained in our customer database for customers who have placed orders in the last 24 months, after which it is permanently deleted.  
If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or if you wish to have your personal information removed from our database, please contact our Privacy officer in one of the following ways:

Email: [privacyofficer@panago.com](mailto:privacyofficer@panago.com)  
Phone: 1.877.997.1234 / Ext.: 6144

  Mail: Panago Pizza Head Office  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
33149 Mill Lake Road  
Abbotsford, BC V2S 2A4
